review_id	cluster_display_id	cluster_internal_id	stars	date	helpful	source	text	question	verdict	reason
bad6e5a4-03e6-433d-b03a-8e241569fbd4	31	1001	1	16-09-2026	0	bucket_recluster	not at all a good app it will not give clear instructions to the customer regarding the order so l have lost my amount	"Is this primarily a late-delivery / cancellation complaint - i.e. does it belong in theme #2, Delivery runs far past the ETA?"	NO	
e2631d67-127f-4781-a547-4135130a70ef	31	1001	1	27-09-2026	0	incremental	worst app ever when i ordered food they took too much time 2 hour and i was starving so i cook by my own and ate it. and now they will charge me of this order on my next order... what a rubbish app	"Is this primarily a late-delivery / cancellation complaint - i.e. does it belong in theme #2, Delivery runs far past the ETA?"	yes	
bc6a3597-5350-4875-ab31-11821c55c4b4	31	1001	1	19-09-2026	0	bucket_recluster	One of the worst delivery apps. Zomato and ownly are way better. They ALWAYS club your orders and it delays for more than an hour. Only their instamart is worth ordering from. Uninstalled and will never install again.	"Is this primarily a late-delivery / cancellation complaint - i.e. does it belong in theme #2, Delivery runs far past the ETA?"	yes	
ffd65dc4-a717-47e8-863c-ff7868a3d145	31	1001	1	17-09-2026	0	bucket_recluster	worst delivery app and response team ever no resolution no reply and then don't even vare about the customers. RUN A uninstall campaign against them	"Is this primarily a late-delivery / cancellation complaint - i.e. does it belong in theme #2, Delivery runs far past the ETA?"	no	
d3683c15-94b6-4316-a387-64ac55191b80	31	1001	1	14-09-2026	0	bucket_recluster	order tracking page not working with this spin update	"Is this primarily a late-delivery / cancellation complaint - i.e. does it belong in theme #2, Delivery runs far past the ETA?"	no	
50a23437-4406-4bf3-a27a-0ee7f178a68f	31	1001	1	17-09-2026	0	bucket_recluster	worst app ever.... u will sleep hungry but they will not deliver food ...	"Is this primarily a late-delivery / cancellation complaint - i.e. does it belong in theme #2, Delivery runs far past the ETA?"	yes 	
4d912d1b-9fc9-40ee-9e1b-b4970c42351b	31	1001	1	19-09-2026	0	bucket_recluster	"very bad first experience. not only this app charges just double of the amount of food price in name of taxes and delivery charges but the actual condition of my food is just speechless. so disappointed that I installed this app. this is neither time saving as it took the most time on delivery out of all food apps I use but the food itself arrived in such bad conditions that had I not been sick, I would have asked for a refund. The drink leaked through package thank god the food was safe stil 👎"	"Is this primarily a late-delivery / cancellation complaint - i.e. does it belong in theme #2, Delivery runs far past the ETA?"	yes	
f3cd6941-352e-4a0e-afc8-fd00db259d73	31	1001	1	19-09-2026	0	bucket_recluster	"the help center is useless. due to the OTP auto read feature, the order was placed twice. and help center didn't do anything."	"Is this primarily a late-delivery / cancellation complaint - i.e. does it belong in theme #2, Delivery runs far past the ETA?"	no	
c3ca566d-8376-4670-9e34-4b849bdaccf3	31	1001	4	16-09-2026	0	bucket_recluster	"When I install the app and open it, why does the default tab start with instamart and not food. And not to mention that it starts with an unskippable notification that says continue with instamart. Why did I install this app then...I already have the instamart app. Small issue I know but annoying. Fix ya'll UI UX guys."	"Is this primarily a late-delivery / cancellation complaint - i.e. does it belong in theme #2, Delivery runs far past the ETA?"	no	
e587448f-9d0a-4ea4-a3ec-0e8444144012	31	1001	1	14-09-2026	0	bucket_recluster	"worst delivery app, No empathy in addressing customer issues"	"Is this primarily a late-delivery / cancellation complaint - i.e. does it belong in theme #2, Delivery runs far past the ETA?"	no	
